Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Consumer Studies, undated, 1927-1969
  - Subseries C: Various, undated, 1928-1969
    - Crossley Inc.--Continuous Consumer Index (CCI)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 736)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 737)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 738)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 739)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 740)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 741)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 742)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 743)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 744)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 745)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 10, 1936 May (Box 14:, Folder 746)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 747)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 748)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 749)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 750)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 751)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 752)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 753)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 754)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 755)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 756)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 11, 1936 June (Box 14:, Folder 757)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 758)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 759)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 760)
      - Cereals--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 761)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 762)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 763)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 764)
      - Flour--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 765)
      - Gelatin--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 766)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 767)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. II, No. 12, 1936 July (Box 15:, Folder 768)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 769)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 770)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 771)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 772)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 773)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 774)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 775)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 776)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 1, 1936 August (Box 15:, Folder 777)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 778)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 779)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 780)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 781)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 782)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 783)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 784)
      - Hand Lotions and Creams--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 785)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 786)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 2, 1936 September (Box 15:, Folder 787)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 788)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 789)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 790)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 791)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 792)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 793)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 794)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 795)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 3, 1936 October (Box 15:, Folder 796)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 797)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 798)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 799)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 800)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 801)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 802)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 803)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 804)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 4, 1936 November (Box 15:, Folder 805)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 806)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. II, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 807)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 808)
      - Cereal--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 809)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 810)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 811)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 812)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 813)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 814)
      - Hand Lotions and Creams--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 815)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 816)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 5, 1936 December (Box 15:, Folder 817)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 818)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 819)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 820)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 821)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 822)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 823)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 824)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 825)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 826)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 6, 1937 January (Box 15:, Folder 827)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 828)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 829)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 830)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 831)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 832)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 833)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 834)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 835)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 836)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 7, 1937 February (Box 15:, Folder 837)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 838)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 839)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 840)
      - Cereals--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 841)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 842)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 843)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 844)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 845)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 846)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 847)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 8, 1937 March (Box 15:, Folder 848)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 849)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 850)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 851)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 852)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 853)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 854)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 855)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 856)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 857)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 9, 1937 April (Box 15:, Folder 858)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 859)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 860)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 861)
      - Cereals--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 862)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 863)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 864)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 865)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 866)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 867)
      - Hand Lotions and Creams--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 868)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 869)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 10, 1937 May (Box 15:, Folder 870)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 871)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 872)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 873)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 874)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 875)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 876)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 877)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 878)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. III, No. 11, 1937 June (Box 15:, Folder 879)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 880)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 881)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 882)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 883)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 884)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 885)
      - Flour--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 886)
      - Gelatin--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 887)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. III, No. 12, 1937 July (Box 15:, Folder 888)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 889)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 890)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 891)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 892)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 893)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 894)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 895)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 896)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 897)
      - Laxatives and Cathartics--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 898)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 1, 1937 August (Box 15:, Folder 899)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 900)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 901)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 902)
      - Coffee and Food Beverages--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 903)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 904)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 905)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 906)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 907)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 2, 1937 September (Box 15:, Folder 908)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 909)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 910)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 911)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 912)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 913)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 914)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 915)
      - Hand Lotions and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 916)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 3, 1937 October (Box 15:, Folder 917)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 918)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 919)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 920)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 921)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 922)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 923)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 924)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 4, 1937 November (Box 15:, Folder 925)
      - Canned Fruits and Vegetables--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 926)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 927)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 928)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 929)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 930)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 931)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 932)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 5, 1937 December (Box 16:, Folder 933)
      - Canned Soup--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 934)
      - Canned Tomato and Fruit Juices--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 935)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 936)
      - Dentifrices--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 937)
      - Face Powders and Creams--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 938)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 939)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 940)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 6, 1938 January (Box 16:, Folder 941)
      - Flour--Vol. IV, No. 7, 1938 February (Box 16:, Folder 942)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 8, 1938 April (Box 16:, Folder 943)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 8, 1938 April (Box 16:, Folder 944)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 8, 1938 April (Box 16:, Folder 945)
      - Cereals--Vol. IV, No. 9, 1938 June (Box 16:, Folder 946)
      - Gelatin--Vol. IV, No. 9, 1938 June (Box 16:, Folder 947)
      - Soaps and Cleansers--Vol. IV, No. 9, 1938 June (Box 16:, Folder 948)
    - Crowell-Collier Publishing Co.--Automotive Survey, 1949 October (Box 16:, Folder 949)
    - Crowell-Collier Publishing Co.--Best Make of Automotive Body Survey (tabulations only), 1950 December (Box 16:, Folder 950)
    - Cunningham and Walsh, Inc.--Company Name Familiarity Survey, 1952 March (Box 16:, Folder 951)
    - C-Z Chemical Co.--Marvene Soap Stocks Inventory Study (tabulations only), 1946 April (Box 16:, Folder 952)
    - Davenport Hosiery Mills, Inc.--Hosiery Study (qualitative analysis only), 1943 [November] (Box 16:, Folder 953)
    - Dole Corp.--National Canned Pineapple and Pinapple Juice Consumer Study Proposal, 1963 July (Box 16:, Folder 954)
    - Doremus and Co.--Midtown Manhattan Weather Star Recognition Survey, 1951 February (Box 16:, Folder 955)
    - Doremus and Co.--Midtown Manhattan Weather Star Recognition Survey, 1951 November (Box 16:, Folder 956)
    - Duane Jones Co.--Shaving Cream Brand Selection Influence Survey, 1945 September (Box 16:, Folder 957)
    - Duane Jones Co.--Cleanser Product Test, 1950 August (Box 16:, Folder 958)
    - Esso Standard Oil Co.--Gas Station Owner/Lesee Relations with Suppliers Study, 1949 August (Box 16:, Folder 959)
    - Esso Standard Oil Co.--The Meaning of CALSO Study, 1949 September - October (Box 16:, Folder 960)
    - F. and M. Schaefer Brewing Co.
      - Taste Test Survey (tabulations only, with supplemental data), 1951 September - October (Box 16:, Folder 961)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, Connecticut tabulations, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 962)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, Massachusetts tabulations, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 963)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, New Jersey tabulations, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 964)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, New York tabulations, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 965)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, Pennsylvania tabulations, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 966)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study, 1952 December (Box 16:, Folder 967)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study Marketing Data, 1952 December (Box 16:, Folder 968)
      - Schaefer Housewife Study Press Releases, undated (Box 16:, Folder 969)
    - Foote, Cone and Belding--Smoking Habits of Tobacco Marketing Men Study, Correspondences, 1947 October - 1953 December (Box 16:, Folder 970)
    - Foote, Cone and Belding--Smoking Habits of Tobacco Marketing Men Study, 1947 December (Box 16:, Folder 971)
    - Fortune Magazine--Truck Buying Procedures Study, 1952 November (Box 16:, Folder 972)
    - Frozen Food Products, Inc.--Westchester County Frozen Food Market Study, 1947 September (Box 16:, Folder 973)
    - Fuller, Smith and Ross--Transportation Study (Wave No. 1), 1950 July (Box 16:, Folder 974)
    - Fuller, Smith and Ross--Transportation Study (Wave No. 2), 1950 July (Box 16:, Folder 975)
    - Fuller, Smith and Ross--Westinghouse Radio Marketing Research Proposal, 1945 October (Box 16:, Folder 976)
    - General Electric Co.--Correspondence Re:Lost Sales Study Proposal, 1949 June (Box 16:, Folder 977)
    - General Foods Corp.--Stockholder Survey, 1944 February (Box 16:, Folder 978)
    - General Foods Corp.--Comparison of General Foods Products in the Pantries of Stockholders Study, 1949 March (Box 16:, Folder 979)
    - General Motors--Productivity of General Motors Automobile Advertising Research Proposal, 1962 December (Box 16:, Folder 980)
    - Geyer Newell and Ganger, Inc.--A Name Study Proposal, 1948 June (Box 16:, Folder 981)
    - Good Luck Margarine--Margarine Taste Preferences of Home Economists Survey (tabulations only), 1951 June (Box 16:, Folder 982)
    - Good Luck Margarine--Margarine Taste Preferences of Women's Club Members Survey, 1951 July (Box 16:, Folder 983)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., Inc.--Airship Audiences Study, 1946 July (Box 16:, Folder 984)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., Inc.--Airship Audiences Study, 1947 August - September (Box 16:, Folder 985)
    - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Co., Inc.--Check-back on Goodyear Purchase Intentions Study, 1952 April (Box 16:, Folder 986)
    - Gorham Manufacturing Co.--Silver Flatware Opinion Study, 1944 October (Box 16:, Folder 987)
    - Grove Laboratories, Inc.--Treatment For Colds Study, 1947 August (Box 16:, Folder 988)
    - Gulf Brewing Co.--Advertising Impression Study Proposal, 1948 June (Box 16:, Folder 989)
    - Hall Brothers, Inc.--Radio Advertising Survey (no formal analysis), undated (Box 17:, Folder 990)
    - Hamilton Watch Co.--Research Proposal, 1953 February (Box 17:, Folder 991)
    - Hamilton Watch Co.--Consumer Preference Study Plan, 1953 December (Box 17:, Folder 992)
    - H.B. Humphrey Co.--Post-War Private Flying Survey, 1944 January (Box 17:, Folder 993)
    - House Beautiful Magazine--Appliance Ownership Study (draft), 1948 December (Box 17:, Folder 994)
    - Ingersoll-Waterbury Clock Co.--Watches and Clocks Study, 1943 October (Box 17:, Folder 995)
    - Institute of Public Relations, Inc.--Milk Consumers' Opinions of Delivery Schedules Survey: New York, NY, 1945 September (Box 17:, Folder 996)
    - Intercontinent Corp.--U.S. Trade in Spices and Coir Study (tabulations only), 1948 May (Box 17:, Folder 997)
    - Irving Trust Co.--Public Attitudes Toward Lending Institutions Pilot Study, 1947 March (Box 17:, Folder 998)
    - Italian Line--Christmas Cruise Patrons Study, undated (Box 17:, Folder 999)
    - James Lees and Sons Co.--Research Proposal, 1953 March (Box 17:, Folder 1000)
    - J.B. Ford Sales Co.--Analysis of Sales Potentials Proposal, 1941 February (Box 17:, Folder 1001)
    - J.D. Thrasher and Co.
      - Pilot Razor Blade Consumers Survey, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1002)
      - Teenage Copy Test Study (tabulations only), undated (Box 17:, Folder 1003)
      - Gin Brand Sales Survey, 1946 January (Box 17:, Folder 1004)
      - Personna Razor Blade Display Test (tabulations only), 1946 April (Box 17:, Folder 1005)
      - Stocks of Personna Razor Blades Study (tabulations only), 1946 April (Box 17:, Folder 1006)
      - Retail Liquor Outlets Survey: Atlantic City, NJ, 1946 June (Box 17:, Folder 1007)
      - Tea Packaging Method Preferences Study: Newark, NJ, 1946 July (Box 17:, Folder 1008)
      - Tea Packing Method Preferences Study: Brooklyn and Bronx, NY, 1946 September (Box 17:, Folder 1009)
    - Jell-O--Package Design Study Plan, 1952 March (Box 17:, Folder 1010)
    - J.G. White Engineering Corp.--Railroad Customer Attitude Study: Long Island, NY, 1947 January (Box 17:, Folder 1011)
    - J.G. White Engineering Corp.--Passengers of the Long Island Railroad Study, 1948 December (Box 17:, Folder 1012)
    - J.G. White Engineering Corp.--Passengers of the Long Island Railroad Study (Reference Materials), undated (Box 17:, Folder 1013)
    - [ J.M. Mathes, Inc.]-- New York State Milk Consumption Survey (tabulations only), 1941 March (Box 17:, Folder 1014)
    - J. Walter Thompson Co.
      - Unidentified Study Visual Aids, undated (Box 17:, Folder 1015)